const data = [
  {
    week: 1,
    questions: [
      {
        question: `Communication between a computer and a keyboard involves ______________ transmission`,
        options: [`Simplex`, `Full-duplex`, `Automatic`, `Half-duplex`],
        answer: `Half-duplex`,
      },
      {
        question: `The structure or format of data is called ___________`,
        options: [`Formatting`, `Struct`, `Semantics`, `Syntax`],
        answer: `Syntax`,
      },
      {
        question: `A _______ is the physical path over which a message travels.`,
        options: [`Protocol`, `Medium`, `Route`, `Path`],
        answer: `Medium`,
      },
      {
        question: `A _________ set of rules that govern data communication.`,
        options: [`Protocols`, `Servers`, `Standards`, `RFCs`],
        answer: `Protocols`,
      },
      {
        question: `How many layers are present in the Internet protocol stack (TCP/IP model)?`,
        options: [`10`, `7`, `6`, `5`],
        answer: `5`,
      },
      {
        question: `Which type of topology is best suited for large businesses which must carefully control and coordinate the operation of distributed branch outlets?`,
        options: [`Ring`, `Hierarchical`, `Star`, `Local Area`],
        answer: `Hierarchical`,
      },
      {
        question: `Physical or logical arrangement of network is __________`,
        options: [`Topology`, `Control`, `Routing`, `Networking`],
        answer: `Topology`,
      },
      {
        question: `Data communication system within a building or campus is________`,
        options: [`MAN`, `WAN`, `PAN`, `LAN`],
        answer: `LAN`,
      },
      {
        question: `Communication channel is shared by all the machines on the network in ________`,
        options: [
          `anycast network`,
          `unicast network`,
          `broadcast network`,
          `multicast network`,
        ],
        answer: `broadcast network`,
      },
      {
        question: `A __________ is a device that forwards packets between networks by processing the routing information included in the packet.`,
        options: [`bridge`, `hub`, `firewall`, `router`],
        answer: `router`,
      },
    ],
  },
];

export default data;
